Ok. To start off your nail art, if the person that you're doing nail art on, or if you're doing it on yourself, you're going to need to remove any nail polish that is on the natural nail, or on the acrylic nail.
To do that, you start by getting a lint free cotton ball.
You prefer lint free just because you don't want any little hairs, or any little pieces of anything getting into the polish to mess up your design.
You're going to take your polish remover, also known as acetone.
Saturate your cotton ball with it, and then you're going to start removing the polish from all ten nails.
When you use a lint free cotton ball, it tends to make clean up a little less messy.
You can get into all the crevices a little easier.
And you're just going to start taking the polish off one nail at a time.
If you happen to see any fuzz left over, just pull it off.
I like to start by starting with the pinkie nail and working into the thumb.
It just makes it easier, if you have a little system to go through.
And as you take it off, make sure that there's not any polish left over on the fingernail itself.
You may also have to actually go underneath the nail, to get any excess polish off.
And then once you've removed the polish from all ten nails, you'll be ready to start your nail art design.
And this is how you just take off the polish.
Off of all ten nails.